Poco, what were you doing
wandering about at this hour?!
P-Papa…
At least you're safe.
Where's Sis?
She went out to look for you.
She… She left the house?!
Poco, what's the matter?
You're acting strange.
Sis!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters
swirling light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man
who follows his ambition…
…a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
EPISODE 8:
"BLOODY BATTLE! JOJO & DIO"
For instance…
Behold this lovely rose.
You, my dear, are like this rose.
Pay attention, mademoiselle.
Once this flower blooms,
it will soon wither away.
Such a pity, is it not?
What a wonderful age, sixteen!
So pure and innocent!
Brimming with delicious energy
isn't she, Lord Dio!
The ill-mannered
are unworthy of life.
So, mademoiselle…
I offer you a choice.
I can make you young
and beautiful for all eternity.
However, I am not one to force affection.
You are free to choose
your own destiny.
Devil.
What? I couldn't quite hear.
You're a damned d-devil!
Curse you forever!
How regrettable
our little rendezvous must end.
May I introduce you to…
…the dreaded Doobie.
Since I am not to your liking,
I wish you joy with him.
Farewell, mademoiselle.
W-Who's there?!
Who indeed?
I will not give a zombie
the honor of hearing my name!
Sis!
Poco!
I bit 'em! I bit 'em!
Bit 'em lots!
There's something
beneath that mask of his!
What in the…
That zombie is full of snakes!
Venomous cobras
and flesh-eating vipers!
Surprised, are you?
Those snakes bit his face,
and not just once!
Not again.
I don't have time for
your sick games, Dio!
Impressive.
He managed to extract the poison.
Extraordinary that he can control
his blood flow after only brief training.
Before passing, Baron Zeppeli
gave his own life energy to Mr. Joestar.
I'll use a bit of Hamon
to boil the blood of those snakes!
Sis!
Poco!
I'm back from hell, Dio.
Still alive, JoJo?
I suppose that means
you've defeated my two knights.
Lord Dio, we await your order
to eliminate him!
Allow me to scar his flesh
with my fangs!
Dio!
No. This one…
This one belongs to me, Dio!
Allow me to be frank, JoJo.
I didn't want to have to
do this myself.
We were raised together
under the same roof.
I do not delight in turning you
into my undead servant.
That's why I left this business
to my knights.
But I underestimated you.
Seeing you alive makes me realize
I was too soft a ruler.
Which is why I have no misgivings
about slaughtering you now!
The feeling is mutual.
I feel no guilt in burying you today!
By the way, what became
of your mustachioed friend
with the gaudy hat?
Did he run off?
Dio, I shall confess.
It pains me as a gentleman, but…
…I, Jonathan Joestar,
am going to kill you, Dio,
out of revenge!
Come, JoJo!
Dire!
JoJo, stand aside.
My time to exact revenge is now.
Zeppeli and I went through two decades
of harsh training together.
Dio, I shall send you
to the depths of hell!
Wait! Dio has hidden abilities!
Hmmm… you have interesting moves.
So this is what you humans
can do with enough training.
In just one night, I have surpassed
the abilities of all men!
Ha! You think you can defeat me
with that tired routine?!
You fell for it, fool!
Thunder Cross Split Attack!
Incredible! By crossing his arms he can
attack while keeping his guard up!
It's the perfect move!
No fighter has ever escaped it.
He's…!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
I-I can't move!
He flash froze him!
Dio vaporized his body's moisture,
freezing him instantly!
Dire can't send Hamon into Dio
unless his blood is flowing!
He's a monster!
He's frozen almost Dire's entire body!
Y-You…
So feeble!
Did you really think your pathetic self
stood a chance against me?! Fool!
So you've all come to
die like dogs!
Allow me to present you with
the most scrumptiously savage death!
- D-Dire!
- Stop!
JoJo, it's time.
I'll be sending you
into oblivion next!
Dire!
I imbued that rose with Hamon.
Feel its thorns?
Dire!
How…
How dare you scar my face?!
Dire…
Speedwagon!
Here!
Dio, I now know how to overwhelm
your freezing attack,
and how to use
my Hamon against you.
All thanks to Dire.
I'll transfer my Hamon to
Blueford's sword of luck and pluck!
How dare you use that vile…
…that vile Hamon on me!
You've pushed your luck far enough!
Enjoy becoming zombie feed!
They'll tear your frightened faces
straight off!
So this is Dio!
The most evil, most despicable being
the world has ever seen!
That composed, refined persona
was just a guise!
Now that he's had a humiliating taste
of Hamon, we witness a true demon!
I will show you no mercy!
I am Pajyu!
Jones!
Pluton!
Barnum!
Needle Vein Strike!
Roses are living things,
so Hamon will remain inside of them.
But steel is different.
I have to maintain contact.
There is a great horde of them.
I'll handle them for you.
As far as I can tell,
Dio is as swift as a leopard.
Thanks to Baron Zeppeli,
Jonathan just might keep up.
But Dio is strong enough to
pulverize flesh and bone with ease!
The battle will end
the moment they meet!
I'll squeeze the life out of you!
I shall rid the world
of your demonic ambition!
When did he grab
those roses!
Now!
Good show!
He snuck around to Dio's right,
his blind side!
D-Damn! JoJo is a veteran fighter!
Y-Yes!
He finally defeated Dio!
Wrong,
you fools!
I-I…
I'm frozen!
So feeble!
Now you will become
one of my servants of the night!
Your carotid is quiet supple
between my fingers!
It's so pleasantly pliant and warm.
I must kick!
My legs are frozen, too!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
Give up, JoJo!
Move and your delicate vein
will burst!
Just a wee prick, and then
your blood for my vampiric essence!
W-We have to help!
Zombies!
Keep those peasants back
for a moment.
They keep coming.
We won't be able to help.
Behold, JoJo, my vampiric essence
as it transforms you into my servant!
You haven't won yet, Dio!
You've made a crucial mistake!
And how so?
To extract my life force,
you haven't completely frozen me!
I can't use my Hamon
if my body is frozen,
but you can't drain
my life energy, either!
Your tactics are flawed!
He's thawing the sword
in the flame!
That blade is conducting the heat
faster than I can freeze it!
He's sending Hamon
through the blade!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
Take this!
He got him!
Look again! You can tell that
the Hamon didn't go through.
My arm…
My arm is frozen again!
It froze just by making contact
with his face!
You underestimate me, JoJo!
I, Dio, respect the explosiveness
of your spirit.
And, I must admit,
that your use of fire was quiet clever.
But JoJo, nothing can escape
my icy grasp.
A single touch to
the arm is all it takes.
I can freeze your entire body
in two seconds.
He expelled the vampiric essence!
Mr. Joestar hasn't given up yet!
Why so tense?
Still looking for a fight?
You can resist all you want,
but you're still just a human.
Your Hamon training is useless!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
A monkey cannot stand
against a human!
You are nothing but
a pathetic monkey, JoJo!
Wrong! With enough conviction,
anything is possible!
Humans learn and evolve!
Let me demonstrate!
You won't, because
you'll soon be a zombie!
His hand, his hand is on fire!
He lit his glove on fire!
With that, he might be able
to defeat Dio's freezing attack!
At long last, we learn who wins
and who loses!
The end has come, Dio!
H-He was blocked?!
No!
He's breaking through!
My body… it's melting away!
The pain! The burning!
I was supposed to live
for centuries… forever!
You had to be destroyed, Dio.
I, Dio…
He fired a liquid death-beam
from his eye!
A few centimeters to the right,
and my brain would've been toast!
Blimey!
That, my friend, is what a dying
and desperate demon looks like.
Dio's plunging down the cliff!
Dio…
He's fainted!
He's spent. And well he should be.
Tonight's battle claimed
too many lives.
But why is he shedding tears
for the bad guy?
Because they grew up together.
But me? I can smile happily!
Are you watching, Baron Zeppeli?
He did it!
Mr. Joestar finally did it!
Dio is dead.
I don't care what anyone says.
The world has been saved!
NEXT EPISODE
What a joyous occasion!
These are tears of joy.
R-Run…
I want to stay like this forever.
Is my new body here?
EPISODE 9:
"THE FINAL RIPPLE!"